## **MUHAMMAD ISMAIL**

<u>+6289687601023</u> | <u>muhaisim7@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/muhismail015</u> | github.com/muhismail015 | Portfolio: muhismail.me | Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat

#### INTRODUCTION

I am a full-stack web developer who graduated with a degree in information engineering. Experience working on projects through Independent Study in the Kampus Merdeka program, volunteering, and collaborative projects. As an adaptable learner, I have successfully tackled various problem-solving challenges both individually and as part of a team. I am motivated to continue growing and contributing.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# PT. Kinema Systrans Multimedia | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2023 - Dec 2023)

Full-stack Web Developer

- Design website pages using Figma.
- Implement design and create website using ReactJS Vite.
- Design databases and build APIs using NodeJS and Express.js.
- Set up and deploying website using Virtual Machine from Google Cloud Platform.

# PT. Nurul Fikri Cipta Inovasi | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2022 - Dec 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- Collaborate project using Github.
- Layouting template website content.
- Implement design and build APIs using Laravel.
- Deploy and hosting website that have been finished into Webmin.

#### Pemira STT-NF | (Volunteer)

(Jan 2022 - Mei 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- Collaborate project using GitHub
- Design and create website pages for admin dashboard using Laravel.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri - Depok, Indonesia

(2020 - 2024)

Bachelor in Information Engineering (GPA 3.86 / 4.00)

SMK Al-Hasra - Depok, Indonesia

Computer and Network Engineering

(2017 - 2020)

#### **SKILLS**

Hard Skill: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, Python.

Soft Skill: Team Works, Problem Solving, and Time Management.

Software Skill:

- Frameworks & Libraries: NodeJS, ReactJS Vite, Express.js, Laravel.
- Tools: Postman, Figma, GitHub, VSCode.

#### FEATURED PROJECTS

- <u>SuikaBot</u> A WhatsApp Bot with many usefull feature and integrated with AI using Google Gemini AI and Google Imagen.
- AuliaMotorManagement A website to manage inventory and financial data for Aulia Motor Workshop.
- Walntip A project to see one time view message from WhatsApp, using Whatsapp-Web-js. Soon integrated in website version.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Web Development Infinite Learning (MSIB Batch 5), 02 January 2024
- Full-stack Web Developer Academy NF Computer (MSIB Batch 3), 31 December 2022
- Full-stack Web Development PKS Digital School (Bootcamp), 18 December 2021